vieodesign.com 2015-12-27

# Privacy Policy -

#### Effective Date 2011

VIEO Design™, LLC (“we” or “us”) recognizes that you care how information about you is used and shared. We have created this Privacy Policy to inform you of our information collection, use and sharing practices for this website. Please also review our [Terms & Conditions ](http://www.vieodesign.com/refunds-and-cancellations/ "Refunds and Cancellations")which also govern your use of this website.

Please be advised that the practices described in this Privacy Policy apply only to information gathered through this website and, where applicable, through our Customer Service Department in connection with this website, and do not necessarily reflect our practices with respect to information gathered through other websites that we operate or through other off-line means.

If you have any questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact our Customer Service Department.

#### What Information About Me Is Collected and Stored?

We collect and store information that you enter into this website or that you provide to our Sales or Project Management team. For example, when you open an account or place an order, we collect and store some or all of the following information that you provide: name, billing address, shipping address, email address, telephone number, credit card number and expiration date.

This information is used to provide the products and services that you have ordered or requested, to process orders, to send order confirmations and to provide customer service. This information also may be used for our own marketing and internal business purposes, and to contact you about sales, special offers and new site features, unless you have opted not to receive promotional communications in connection with this website.

We collect and store certain other information automatically whenever you interact with this website. For example, we collect your IP address, browser information and reference site domain name every time you visit this website. We also collect information regarding customer traffic patterns and site usage. This information is used to analyze and improve this website and to provide our customers with a fulfilling shopping experience.

Also, like many websites, we use “cookies”, which are files stored on your computer’s hard drive by your browser. Cookies do not contain personally identifiable information. Cookies help us to identify account holders and to optimize their shopping experience. Cookies also allow us to hold selections in a shopping cart when a user leaves this website without checking out. Cookies are not used on this website to store your account information; this information is stored securely on this website’s server. When you log in at this website  with your username and password, we will assign you a secure session id. The server then passes your information to you through this secure session id. Also, we will use cookies to monitor and maintain information about your use of this website. Cookies are also used to track the identity of the website you visited immediately prior to visiting this website; otherwise, we do not track information about your use of other websites. Most browsers accept cookies automatically but allow you to disable them. We recommend that you leave cookies “turned on” so that we can offer you a better shopping experience on this website. We also may collect and store information about you that we receive from other sources, to enable us to update and correct the information contained in our database and to provide product recommendations and special offers that we think will interest you.

#### Is Information Collected From Children?

This website is not intended or directed to anyone under the age of 18. We do not sell any items ordered through this website directly to anyone who we know to be under the age of 18, nor do we collect any personal information from anyone who we know to be under the age of 18. If you are under the age of 18, you should use this website only with the involvement of a parent or guardian and should not submit any personal information to us.

#### With Whom Do You Share Information?

We do not share with others, or sell or rent to others, any personal information that you provide to us through this website or through our Customer Service Department, except with your consent or as described in this Privacy Policy.

We engage third parties to perform services in connection with the operation of our business. Examples of these services include payment processing and authorization, fraud protection and credit risk reduction, product customization, marketing and promotional material distribution, website evaluation, data analysis and, where applicable, data cleansing. We provide personal information to these third parties, but we authorize them to use this information only in connection with the services they perform.

We may release personal information if we believe in good faith that: the law or legal process requires it; we have received a valid administrative request from a law enforcement agency; or such release is necessary to protect the rights, property or safety of VIEO Design llc, or any of our respective affiliates, business partners, customers or others.

We may share non-personal information with our marketing partners, advertisers and others from time to time. Examples of such non-personal information include the number of users who visited this website during a specific time period or purchased a specific product through this website. This information generally is shared in an aggregated form.

As with any business, it is possible that as our business develops, we might sell or buy online assets. In such transactions, information about customers often is among the transferred assets. Accordingly, in the event that VIEO Design llc, or substantially all of our respective assets, are acquired by a third party, such information may be one of the transferred assets (unless the information was collected under a previous Privacy Policy that did not permit such disclosure). Under such circumstances VIEO Design llc would to the extent possible require the acquiring party to follow the practices described in this Privacy Policy.

#### What Steps Are Taken To Keep Personal Information Secure?

We use various security measures, including Secure Socket Layer (SSL) encryption technology, to protect personal information that we collect. If you place an order through this website, you will be asked to set up an account and provide an email address and password. You must provide an appropriate email address and password in order to access account information. In order to help protect your personal information further, you should be careful about providing your password to others. If you wish to cancel a password, or if you become aware of any loss, theft or unauthorized use of a password, please contact our Customer Service Department.

#### What Happens When I Link To or From Another website?

This website may contain links to websites operated by third parties. Please be advised that the practices described in this Privacy Policy do not apply to information gathered through these other websites. We encourage you to be aware of when you leave this website and to read the privacy policies of each and every website that you visit.

If you have accessed this website through a link from certain of our advertising or marketing partners, this website may include a frame of the applicable advertising or marketing partner. Nevertheless, the information you provide to us through these framed Web pages is collected by us, and our use of this information is governed by this Privacy Policy.

#### What About Contests and Sweepstakes?

When we run a contest or sweepstakes relating to this website, it will be accompanied by a set of rules. The rules for each contest/sweepstakes will specify how the information gathered from you for entry will be used and disclosed.

#### What About Online Surveys?

We may from time to time conduct on-line surveys. When you complete an online survey, we may ask for certain information including your age, zip code, shopping habits, email and/or mailing address. This information will be treated in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

#### How Will I Be Informed About Changes Regarding This Privacy Policy?

If we make any material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will post a notice on this website notifying users of the changes. In some cases, we also may send an email notifying users of the changes. You should check this website periodically to see if any recent changes to this Privacy Policy have occurred.
